Well, we are now at the end of this course and I hope you should have properly learned
how to use DockerNSP.net core apps.
I covered almost every essential part which .NET developers should know about Docker
life, Docified, Docker Compose networking between different containers, multi containers
and so on.
Time flies away and so these three hours of this course.
This is my first course ever and I am very excited to publish this course for people
like you.
I have made my serious efforts and best efforts are put to all my knowledge which I have
and experience to make this course a good value for your money.
It covers all the topics which you will ever need as a .NET developer.
Although if you are in DevOps then you will have to cover much more of Docker topics.
The best way is to learn from Docker official website where you will get up-to-date learning
on all the topics, how to get the best of this course.
You will have to implement all the topics covered in this course not once but three times.
That will give you enough confidence to implement your .NET projects on Docker.
If you are a working professional then I suggest you to keep at least two hours of your
time daily to implement all these topics on the course and in less than five days you
will have covered three times all the topics on this course.
So I can say in less than one week you will become a very good software developer in
Docker.
If you are non working then you can complete all these topics in just three days.
How to solve problems for any errors which you get copy the errors and paste it on Google
to find the different solutions.
Stack Overflow is one such website where you will find every problem solution.
You can even post your questions along with the errors which you are getting on Stack
Overflow.
Note that your questions should be in details as Stack Overflow will not let you to post
your questions.
Your questions should be in details with screenshots of errors, your whole process in points,
have the solution which you have tried then you can expect good answers from Stack Overflow
community.
I would like to show one such question which I asked on Stack Overflow regarding Docker
sometime back.
So this is the question.
Look at the question it has given in details with the procedures in points which I have
followed.
I have also provided screenshots of the errors which I am getting and the different
solutions which I have cried.
I was able to solve this problem through the answers given by community members.
This is how you should post your questions on Stack Overflow.
I can also help you if you get any such problem regarding Docker and ASP.NET Core.
You can contact me on Udemy or on X.
My link is at Yogi hosting.
In the end I would like to say congratulations you have completed this course and have
a nice and bright career.